Igor Franciuc, Frontend Developer

E-mail: igor.franciuc@gmail.com
Phone: +373 69 054 697
Telegram: https://t.me/lfeerus

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/igor-franchiuc-890308242

Website: https://igor-franchiuc.netlify.app/

Chisinau (Moldova).



About me

I have experience in creating website layouts, where I honed my HTML, CSS and JavaScript skills. However, I want to grow and I think it would be more effective for me to become a member of a friendly team as a Frontend Developer.

I have studied React, Javascript, HTML, CSS and am currently mastering TypeScript. In my free time I love to learn new technologies, create pet projects, play the guitar and go to the gym.

I'm ready to work, learn, get better and grow every day with great people.

Skills

Technical Skills

React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS, JQuery, Webpack, MySql, PHP, Git, Figma, Photoshop.

Language Skills

Russian (mother tongue), English (B2), Romanian (B2)

Soft Skills

Open to communication, a team player, receptive to learning, reserved, reasonable.

Work Experience

SANtech (Frontend Developer - internship)

May, 2022 — July, 2022

Learning the basics of web development. Stack: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript

Studio Webmaster (Web Developer)

August, 2022 — November, 2022

Experience in rebuilding websites and developing online stores.

Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Web Developer (VVT Group Inc.)

May, 2023 — present

Website development for US clients. Creating lendings, multi-page websites, working with hosting and mail. Stack: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, React.js

Education

Higher education

September, 2021 — Current

Applied Informatics, Technical University of Moldova (https://utm.md/), Chisinau (Moldova)

Courses

September, 2022 — February, 2023

"A complete course in JavaScript + React - from scratch to results" by Ivan Petrichenko (https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-1dc80c7e-c9eb-4bc5-bbfe-65b8f064eb70/), Chisinau (Moldova) September, 2017 — May, 2020

English courses: "Basic English", Chisinau (Moldova)